# Role
You are an Expert Senior Python Backend Developer specializing in `discord.py` (Asynchronous programming), `SQLite`, and complex GraphQL APIs.

# Project Context
We are building an AI Tournament Organizer for a Street Fighter 6 online tournament. 
This is Phase 1: Setting up the project structure, Database, Discord Bot core, and Start.gg API integration.

# Required Tech Stack
- Python 3.10+
- `discord.py` (for the bot)
- `aiosqlite` (Async SQLite database to avoid blocking the Discord event loop)
- `httpx` or `aiohttp` (Async HTTP requests for Start.gg API)
- `python-dotenv` (for loading API keys)

# Task 1: Database Setup (`database.py`)
Create an async SQLite database setup.
- Table name: `players`
- Columns: 
  - `discord_id` (TEXT, Primary Key)
  - `startgg_id` (TEXT, Unique)
  - `startgg_tag` (TEXT)
  - `cfn_id` (TEXT) # Capcom Fighters Network ID for SF6
- Write async helper functions: `register_player()`, `get_player_by_discord()`, `get_player_by_startgg()`.

# Task 2: Start.gg API Wrapper (`startgg_api.py`)
Create an async class `StartGGClient`. Read the `STARTGG_TOKEN` from `.env`.
Implement the following GraphQL operations using `httpx`:
1. `get_ready_matches(tournament_slug: str)`: 
   - Write a GraphQL Query to fetch sets in the tournament where `state: 2` (called/ready to play).
   - Return a list of dictionaries containing: `set_id`, `entrant1_id`, `entrant2_id`.
2. `report_match_result(set_id: int, winner_id: int, score: str)`:
   - Write a GraphQL Mutation using `reportBracketSet`.
3. `mark_set_dq(set_id: int, missing_entrant_id: int)`:
   - Write a GraphQL Mutation to DQ the missing player and advance the other.
*Constraint:* Implement a delay or rate-limit handler (Start.gg allows max 80 requests per 60 seconds).

# Task 3: Discord Bot Core (`main.py` & `/cogs/registration.py`)
1. Setup the basic `discord.py` bot with Slash Commands enabled.
2. Create a slash command: `/link [startgg_id] [cfn_id]`.
   - **Logic:** When a user runs this, the bot fetches their Discord ID, saves the `startgg_id` and `cfn_id` into the SQLite DB using the functions from Task 1.
   - **Response:** "âœ… Successfully linked your Start.gg account and SF6 CFN ID."

# Output Requirements
Generate the code for these 3 files. Ensure all code is modular, well-commented, and handles exceptions (like database lock errors or API timeouts).
# Role
You are a Lead AI Engineer and Python Architect, an expert in `LangChain`, `LangGraph`, `discord.py` (Async), and building Event-Driven Agentic workflows with LLM Tool Calling.

# Project Context
This is Phase 2 of the AI Tournament Organizer for Street Fighter 6. 
You will build an Event-Driven State Machine using `LangGraph` that manages matches inside Discord threads. 
Because the Agent needs to wait for human input (Discord messages like "ready" or "I won 2-0"), you MUST use LangGraph's Checkpointing (`MemorySaver`) to pause and resume the graph execution.

# Required Tech Stack
- Python 3.10+
- `langgraph` (with `MemorySaver` for persistence)
- `langchain-core`, `langchain-openai` or `langchain-groq` (For LLM)
- `pydantic` (for strict LLM structured output)
- `discord.py`

# Task 1: State Definition (`agent_state.py`)
Define the state schema using `TypedDict`. The graph state must track:
- `set_id` (int): Start.gg match ID.
- `thread_id` (int): Discord thread ID for this match.
- `player1_discord`, `player2_discord` (int): Discord IDs.
- `player1_ready`, `player2_ready` (bool): Default False.
- `chat_history` (list of strings): Formatted as "PlayerX: message".
- `match_status` (str): 'waiting_checkin', 'playing', 'conflict', 'completed', 'dq'.
- `winner_id` (int | None): Resolved winner.
- `score_string` (str | None): e.g., "2-0".

# Task 2: Pydantic Schema for LLM (`schemas.py`)
Create a strict Pydantic model for the LLM to extract results from chat:
```python
class MatchResultExtraction(BaseModel):
    conflict_detected: bool = Field(description="True if players disagree on who won or the score. False if they agree.")
    winner_discord_id: Optional[int] = Field(description="The Discord ID of the winning player, if clear.")
    score: Optional[str] = Field(description="The match score, e.g., '2-0' or '2-1'.")
    reasoning: str = Field(description="Brief explanation of how the LLM determined this outcome based on chat.")
# Role
You are an Expert Full-Stack Developer specializing in Python (FastAPI), WebSockets, React/Vanilla JS, and Esports Broadcast Overlays (OBS).

# Task
Build Phase 3 of the AI Tournament Organizer. Replace the local AHK script idea with a Real-Time Web Dashboard for the Tournament Organizer (TO) and an Overlay for OBS Studio.

# Core Architecture
1. **Backend:** Use `FastAPI` to serve the web pages and handle API requests. Implement WebSockets for real-time UI updates without page reloads.
2. **Views (Routes):**
   - `/admin`: The Control Panel for the TO.
   - `/overlay`: The OBS Browser Source screen (must have a transparent background).

# Requirements

## 1. Start.gg Data Integration
Create new GraphQL queries to fetch detailed tournament data:
- Tournament Name & Event Name.
- Total number of sets/matches.
- Current Round (e.g., "Winners Semi-Final", "Grand Final").
- Player Details: Team Prefix (Sponsor), Player Name, Country/Region code (for flags), and current score.
- Final Standings (fetch from the phase standings when the tournament ends).

## 2. Admin Dashboard (`/admin`)
Build a UI that displays:
- **Tournament Overview:** Title, current progress, total matches.
- **Current Match:** e.g., "[Team1] Gamer1 VS [Team2] Gamer2".
- **Next Match:** e.g., "Gamer3 VS [Winner of Current Match]".
- **Action Button: "Call Next Match Players"**. 
  - *Logic:* Clicking this button sends a request to the LangGraph AI Agent (from Phase 2) to ping Gamer1 and Gamer2 in Discord, telling them to join the stream lobby.
- **Manual Score Override:** Simple input fields to manually update the score on the OBS overlay before pushing it to Start.gg.
- **Standings View:** A table showing the final placements of the tournament.

## 3. OBS Overlay (`/overlay`)
Build a clean, broadcast-ready UI that automatically updates via WebSockets when the Admin changes data:
- **Background:** `background-color: transparent;`
- **Player Cards (Left & Right):** Shows Country Flag (using country code), Team Prefix, Player Name, and current Match Score.
- **Top Bar:** Shows Tournament Name and Current Round (e.g., "Street Fighter 6 Main Event - Top 8").
- **Animations:** Simple CSS transitions when a player's score increases or when names change.

# Constraints
- Use WebSockets to ensure that when the Admin updates the score or loads the next match, the OBS `/overlay` updates instantly.
- Expose an API endpoint in FastAPI (e.g., `POST /trigger_agent`) that the Admin dashboard calls when the "Call Next Match" button is clicked. This will wake up the LangGraph workflow.
# Role
You are an Expert Frontend Engineer specializing in Real-time Broadcaster Tools and CSS Engine design.

# Task
Upgrade the current static `overlay.html` into a Dynamic Coordinate-Based System with a WYSIWYG Editor. The system must support Google Fonts integration and real-time WebSocket syncing.

# 1. The State Schema (JSON)
The entire overlay must be driven by a single "OverlayState" object. Example structure:
{
  "background_url": "...",
  "global_font_url": "https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Cairo:wght@200..1000&display=swap",
  "global_font_family": "'Cairo', sans-serif",
  "elements": {
    "p1_name": { "x": 100, "y": 200, "fontSize": "32px", "color": "#ffffff", "text": "Gamer1", "visible": true },
    "p1_score": { "x": 150, "y": 250, "fontSize": "48px", "color": "#ff0000", "text": "0", "visible": true },
    "tournament_round": { "x": 960, "y": 50, "fontSize": "24px", "color": "#aaaaaa", "text": "Winners Semis", "visible": true }
  }
}

# 2. Admin Editor Interface (`/admin/editor`)
Create a dashboard page that allows me to:
- **Canvas View:** A 1920x1080 workspace where I can see all elements.
- **Drag & Drop:** Use a library (like `interact.js` or `react-rnd`) to move elements on the canvas. Their (X, Y) coordinates should update in the State.
- **Font Settings:**
    - An input field to paste a **Google Fonts URL** (e.g., the Cairo link).
    - An input for the **Font Family name** (e.g., 'Cairo').
    - The editor must dynamically inject this font so I can preview it.
- **Styling Panel:** When an element is selected, show controls to change its Color, Font Size, and visibility.
- **Manual Override:** Inputs to manually change the text (Player names, Team, etc.).
- **Sync Button:** A button (or auto-sync) to send the current state JSON to the Backend via WebSockets.

# 3. OBS Overlay View (`/obs`)
Create a clean HTML/JS page for OBS:
- **Zero Configuration:** This page only listens to the WebSocket.
- **Dynamic Font Injection:** When a `global_font_url` is received in the JSON, the page must:
    - Check if a `<link>` with this ID exists; if not, create it and append it to `<head>`.
    - Apply the `global_font_family` to the body or specific elements.
- **Absolute Rendering:** Render all elements as `div` or `span` with `position: absolute`, using the (X, Y) from the JSON.
- **Smooth Transitions:** Use CSS `transition: all 0.3s ease;` so that when coordinates or scores change, they "slide" or "fade" into place instead of flickering.

# 4. Backend (FastAPI + WebSockets)
- Create a WebSocket endpoint `/ws/overlay`.
- **Broadcaster logic:** Any state update sent from the `/admin/editor` must be broadcasted to all connected `/obs` clients.
- **Persistence:** Save the current OverlayState (JSON) to a local file (`overlay_config.json`) so it persists even if the server restarts.

# Instructions
Start by implementing the State Schema and the logic to dynamically inject Google Fonts into the head of the document. Then, build the Draggable Editor.
# Role
You are a Senior System Architect.

# Task
Create a "Tournament Hub" inside the Admin Dashboard to manage multiple tournaments and stream slots.

# Core Logic
1. **Tournament Registry:**
   - Add a field: "Add Tournament by Start.gg Slug".
   - When a slug is entered, use the Start.gg API to fetch: Tournament Name, Event Name, Game Type (SF6/Tekken), and Participant List.
   - Store these in the `tournaments` table.

2. **Stream Slot Management:**
   - Create a way to define "Stream Slots" (e.g., Stream 1, Stream 2).
   - Allow the TO to "Map" a tournament to a Stream Slot.
   - **Crucial:** In the Match Queue, add buttons for each ready match: "Assign to Stream 1" and "Assign to Stream 2".
   - When assigned, the system must update the `OverlayState` for THAT specific stream slot.

3. **Discord Context:**
   - When a match is assigned to a stream, the Discord Bot's call message must include the stream name: 
     "ðŸ“¢ Match Called: <@P1> VS <@P2>. Please join **Stream 1** lobby."

4. **Status & History:**
   - Ensure that even if two tournaments use the same "Stream 1", the results are saved correctly to their respective tournament slugs in the database based on the `set_id`.

# UI Requirements
- Use a `Select` menu in the dashboard to switch between viewing different tournaments.
- Add a "Refresh Data" button next to each tournament to re-sync participant lists or registration status from Start.gg.
# Role
You are a Senior System Architect.

# Task
Create a "Tournament Hub" inside the Admin Dashboard to manage multiple tournaments and stream slots.

# Core Logic
1. **Tournament Registry:**
   - Add a field: "Add Tournament by Start.gg Slug".
   - When a slug is entered, use the Start.gg API to fetch: Tournament Name, Event Name, Game Type (SF6/Tekken), and Participant List.
   - Store these in the `tournaments` table.

2. **Stream Slot Management:**
   - Create a way to define "Stream Slots" (e.g., Stream 1, Stream 2).
   - Allow the TO to "Map" a tournament to a Stream Slot.
   - **Crucial:** In the Match Queue, add buttons for each ready match: "Assign to Stream 1" and "Assign to Stream 2".
   - When assigned, the system must update the `OverlayState` for THAT specific stream slot.

3. **Discord Context:**
   - When a match is assigned to a stream, the Discord Bot's call message must include the stream name: 
     "ðŸ“¢ Match Called: <@P1> VS <@P2>. Please join **Stream 1** lobby."

4. **Status & History:**
   - Ensure that even if two tournaments use the same "Stream 1", the results are saved correctly to their respective tournament slugs in the database based on the `set_id`.

# UI Requirements
- Use a `Select` menu in the dashboard to switch between viewing different tournaments.
- Add a "Refresh Data" button next to each tournament to re-sync participant lists or registration status from Start.gg.
# Role
You are a Lead DevOps Engineer. Your goal is to create a seamless "Start and Stop" system for this specific project.

# Task 1: Project Analysis
First, scan the current directory structure to identify:
1. The exact entry point for the FastAPI backend (e.g., `backend/api/main.py`).
2. The exact entry point for the Discord Bot (e.g., `backend/bot/main.py`).
3. The frontend directory and the package manager used (npm/yarn/pnpm).

# Task 2: Create `run.py`
Create a master startup script that:
- **Port Cleanup:** Checks if ports 8000 (API) and 5173 (Frontend) are already in use and kills those processes before starting.
- **Concurrent Startup:** Starts the Backend (using uvicorn), the Discord Bot (using python), and the Frontend (using npm run dev) as background sub-processes.
- **Logging:** Aggregates logs from all three services into the current terminal, prefixing each line with `[API]`, `[BOT]`, or `[WEB]` for easy debugging.
- **PID Persistence:** Saves the PIDs of all started processes into a `.pids.json` file.
- **Auto-stop:** If the user presses Ctrl+C, it should automatically trigger the logic of `stop.py` to ensure no orphaned processes are left running.

# Task 3: Create `stop.py`
Create a shutdown script that:
- Reads the `.pids.json` file.
- Uses the `psutil` library to gracefully terminate the entire process tree (parent and all children) for each saved PID.
- Forces a kill if a process doesn't stop within 5 seconds.
- Deletes the `.pids.json` file after successful cleanup.

# Constraints
- Use `psutil` for cross-platform process management (Windows/Linux/Mac).
- Ensure the scripts use the correct Virtual Environment (`venv`) if it exists in the project.
- Write the scripts in a way that they work regardless of whether the user is in the root directory or inside a subfolder (use absolute paths or smart path detection).

# Instructions
Before writing code, tell me the paths you identified for the API, Bot, and Frontend to confirm you understand the current structure.
# Role
You are a Senior DevOps and Full-Stack Architect. Your task is to build a complete execution and deployment ecosystem for this project.

# Task 1: Comprehensive Project Analysis
First, scan the entire codebase to identify:
1. Entry points for: FastAPI (Backend), Discord Bot, and the Frontend framework.
2. Necessary Environment Variables in `.env`.
3. All dependencies required for `requirements.txt` and `package.json`.

# Task 2: Local Management Scripts (`run.py` & `stop.py`)
Create two robust Python scripts:
- **`run.py`**:
    - **Port Management:** Automatically kill any process on ports 8000 and 5173 before startup.
    - **Multi-Service Launch:** Run Backend, Bot, and Frontend concurrently.
    - **Advanced Logs Management:** Aggregate logs from all three services into the terminal. Each line MUST be prefixed and color-coded: `[API]` (Cyan), `[BOT]` (Magenta), `[WEB]` (Yellow).
    - **PID Persistence:** Save all PIDs to `.pids.json`.
- **`stop.py`**:
    - Use `psutil` to gracefully terminate the entire process tree for the PIDs in `.pids.json`.
    - Ensure a "Force Kill" fallback if processes don't exit gracefully.

# Task 3: Production Deployment (Docker)
Create the necessary configuration for a production environment:
- **`Dockerfile`**: A multi-stage build or separate Dockerfiles for Backend and Frontend.
- **`docker-compose.yml`**: 
    - Orchestrate the Backend, Bot, and Frontend.
    - Setup **Volumes** for `assets/avatars` and the SQLite database to ensure data persistence.
    - Include a restart policy (`restart: always`).

# Task 4: Documentation & Metadata
- Generate a `requirements.txt` including all discovered backend dependencies (plus `psutil` and `httpx`).
- Update or create a `.env.template` with all the necessary keys (Start.gg, Discord, etc.).

# Instructions for the Agent:
1. Confirm the paths you've detected for the services first.
2. Provide the code for `run.py` and `stop.py`.
3. Provide the `Dockerfile` and `docker-compose.yml`.
4. Tell me exactly how to run the system in both "Local Mode" and "Docker Mode".


Please implement the following updates exactly as described:

### 1. Active Match Status Component (UI & Actions)
- **Add a Close (Ã—) Button:** Add a small 'Ã—' icon button at the top-right corner of the Active Match card. When clicked, it should remove the match from the "Active Match Status" section and return it to the "Match Dashboard" lists (e.g., back to 'In Progress' or 'Not Started').
- **Revert Styling:** The current colors and design of the Active Match cards are visually clashing and do not fit the overall dashboard theme. Revert to the older, cleaner design. Ensure the background colors, borders, and text colors perfectly match the global dark/navy theme of the rest of the dashboard.

### 2. Match Dashboard Component (Sorting & Filtering)
Add a new "Controls/Filters Row" directly below the "Match Dashboard" title.
- **TBD Sorting Logic (Crucial):** Across ALL sections (Not Started, Players Called, etc.), modify the sorting logic. Matches where BOTH players are known (P1 & P2 are assigned) MUST always appear at the top of the list. Matches containing "TBD" (To Be Determined) for one or both players must be pushed to the bottom.
- **Hide TBD Checkbox:** Add a checkbox labeled "Hide TBD Matches" in the controls row. When checked, any match card containing a "TBD" player should be hidden from the view entirely.
- **PhaseGroup (Pool) Filter:** If the tournament has multiple `phaseGroup(id)`s (e.g., Pool A1, Pool B2), add a dropdown menu or a horizontal list of checkboxes in the controls row. 
  - It must include a "Select All / Show All" default option.
  - Allowing the Admin to filter the dashboard to only show matches from specific pools.

### 3. Match Card Component (Data Display)
- **Display PhaseGroup Name:** On every individual match card (across all sections), display the name of the `phaseGroup` (e.g., "Pool A1" or "Winners Bracket") so the Admin knows exactly which pool the match belongs to. Place this neatly near the Match ID or Round Name.

### 4. Complete Matches Section (Action Buttons)
- **Remove Redundant Button:** Currently, completed match cards have both a "Reopen" and a "Reset" button which perform the exact same function (calling `markSetAsIncomplete` mutation). **Remove the "Reopen" button entirely.** Keep only the "Reset" button to avoid confusion.

**Deliverables required from you:**
1. Provide the updated React component code for the `MatchCard` (including the X button and PhaseGroup name).
2. Provide the sorting and filtering functions (TypeScript/JavaScript logic) that handle the TBD top/bottom sorting, the "Hide TBD" state, and the PhaseGroup filtering.
3. Provide the updated CSS/Tailwind classes to ensure the Active Match card matches the global dashboard theme.
# Role
You are a Senior Full-Stack Developer and Architect. You are building an AI Tournament Organizer for Street Fighter 6. 

# Task
Phase 1: Setup the Monorepo structure, the SQLite database, and the Start.gg OAuth 2.0 Authentication system.

# Project Structure
Create the following directory structure:
/root
  /backend
    /core           # Database and Shared Logic
    /api            # FastAPI server (OAuth & Dashboard API)
    /bot            # Discord Bot logic
    /assets         # To store processed avatars (500x500)
  /frontend         # (Placeholder for now)
  .env              # Environment variables

# Requirements for Phase 1:

1. **Database (SQLite + aiosqlite):**
   - Create a `players` table: `discord_id` (PK), `startgg_id`, `gamer_tag`, `cfn_id`, `country`, `team`, `avatar_path`, `is_verified` (bool).

2. **FastAPI Server (The OAuth Gateway):**
   - Read Start.gg Client ID and Secret from `AiBotStart.ggApiToken.txt` or `.env`.
   - Implement `GET /login`: Redirects user to Start.gg OAuth page.
   - Implement `GET /callback`: 
     - Receives the code from Start.gg.
     - Exchanges it for an Access Token.
     - Fetches the user's Profile (ID and Tag) from Start.gg API.
     - Updates/Creates the player record in SQLite.
     - Redirects the user to a "Success" page or sends a message to Discord.

3. **Discord Bot (The Onboarding):**
   - Use `discord.py`.
   - Create a command or button in a specific channel named "Registration".
   - When clicked, it sends a DM to the user with their unique `/login` link for Start.gg OAuth.
   - Once the user completes OAuth, the bot should detect the update and ask the user (in DM) to provide their **CFN ID** and **Upload their Avatar**.

4. **Image Processing Skill:**
   - Use `Pillow`. Create a utility function to:
     - Accept an image from Discord.
     - Center-crop it to a square.
     - Resize it to exactly 500x500 pixels.
     - Save it as `backend/assets/avatars/{startgg_id}.png`.

# Instructions
- Use `python-dotenv` for configuration.
- Use `httpx` for async API calls to Start.gg.
- Ensure all database operations are asynchronous.
- Write clean, modular code. Start by generating the `.env` template and the `database.py` file.
